<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CaptivePortalAutoLogin</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="setup_app_description">
        CaptivePortalAutoLogin is an app that lets your phone solve captive portals automatically.
        Captive portals are the websites which have to be solved in order to obtain internet access in public hotspots. 
        \nThis app will run in the background, 
        and as soon as you encounter a network with captive portal, 
        your operating system will notify this app and it will solve the captive portal in the background.
        If a specific network isn\'t supported, 
        you can choose CaptivePortalAutoLogin when signing into the network 
        to capture the process and submit it to have it implemented in the next updates.
    </string>
    <string name="setup_get_started">
        To get started, 
        you will need to grant this app some permissions.
    </string>
    <string name="setup_notification">
        In order to run in the background, 
        this app needs to show a permanent notification.
        \n
        \nOn some devices it is possible to disable only the service notification category 
        without disabling the notification permission in general.
    </string>
    <string name="setup_notification_denied">
        This app cannot work without this permission.
    </string>
    <string name="setup_location">
        This app needs the location permission in order to collect the SSIDs (names) of networks with captive portals.
        WiFi names can be used to deduce the location of the device, 
        which is why Android locks them behind the location permission.
        \n
        \nThis app uses the SSIDs to determine how a network can be solved
        and to record which SSIDs are supported and can be used for automatic connections in the future.
    </string>
    <string name="setup_app_data_collection">
        We collect data about successful and failed attempts to liberate a network.
        We use this data to aggregate supported and detect problematic networks.
        \n
        \nThe data is completely anonymized and can\'t be linked back to your device or identity at all.
        This is also why we can\'t fulfill data deletion requests.
    </string>
</resources>
